Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- New York City Mayoral Personal Papers, 1965-1973; Part II
  - Sid Davidoff (Assistant to the Mayor), 1965-1973; Series XIV; 24 linear feet (57 boxes)
    - Campaign Research Files, 1964-1971
      - Correspondence acknowledged, 1969-1970 (Box 266, Folder 481)
      - Correspondence not acknowledged, 1970 (Box 266, Folder 482)
      - County committee lists, 1964-1969 (Box 266, Folder 483)
      - Democrats for Lindsay, 1969 (Box 266, Folder 484)
      - Drinan, Robert F., 3rd Congressional district, Massachusetts, 1970 (Box 267, Folder 485)
      - Election races, 1970 (Box 267, Folder 486)
      - Finance letters, samples, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 487)
      - Financial situation correspondence (500 layoffs), 1970 (Box 267, Folder 488)
      - Fusion party, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 489)
      - Invitations, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 490-491)
      - Invitation cancellations, 1970 (Box 267, Folder 492)
      - Invitations not accepted, 1970 (Box 267, Folder 493)
      - Invitations proposed, 1966-1968 (Box 267, Folder 494-495)
      - Jewish correspondence, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 496)
      - Jewish press, Jewish vote, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 497)
      - Katzenberg, Jeff, 1970 (Box 267, Folder 498)
      - Legal releases, 1965-1967 (Box 268, Folder 499)
      - Lindsay correspondence, 1970 (Box 268, Folder 500)
      - Lindsay record, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 501)
      - Lindsay, special letters, 1971 (Box 268, Folder 502)
      - Madison Avenue, 1971 (Box 268, Folder 503)
      - Manhattan, Congressional district, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 504)
      - Manhattan, Democrats for Lindsay, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 505)
      - Manhattan, Mark Gorsten, Dave Arens, Gil Rosa, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 506)
      - Mayor's correspondence, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 507)
      - Meir, Golda, visit, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 508)
      - Memoranda, relocation of offices, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 509)
      - Memoranda, to staff, 1969 (Box 268, Folder 510)
      - Memoranda, supplies, 1966 (Box 268, Folder 511)
      - Memoranda, Robert Sweet, 1967 (Box 268, Folder 512)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1966 (Box 268, Folder 513)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 269, Folder 514-518)
      - Motorala, 1969 (Box 269, Folder 519)
      - New Brunswick Congressional, New Jersey, Kaden, 1970 (Box 269, Folder 520)
      - Nixon, Richard, 1968 (Box 269, Folder 521)
      - Nixon, Richard, against, 1968 (Box 269, Folder 522)
      - Nixon, Richard, for (Box 269, Folder 523)
      - Parades, 1971 (Box 270, Folder 524)
      - Party affiliation correspondence, 1971 (Box 270, Folder 525)
      - Patton, Kenneth, 1971 (Box 270, Folder 526)
      - Pedestrian Mall experiment, 1971 (Box 270, Folder 527)
      - Political comments, letters, memoranda, 1970 (Box 270, Folder 528)
      - Political correspondence, 1971 (Box 270, Folder 529)
      - Political correspondence acknowledged, 1970 (Box 270, Folder 530)
      - Political material, Muskie, McGovern, 1970-1971 (Box 270, Folder 531)
      - Primary campaign, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 532)
      - Primary campaign polling places, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 533)
      - Primary campaign unions, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 534)
      - Primary college coordinators, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 535)
      - Primary councilmatic races, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 536)
      - Primary day, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 537)
      - Projects after election, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 538)
      - Puerto Ricans for Lindsay, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 539)
      - Queens, memoranda, 1967-1968 (Box 270, Folder 540)
      - Queens, primary, Al Ungar, 1969 (Box 270, Folder 541)
      - Registration drive, 1971 (Box 271, Folder 542)
      - Republican politics, 1969 (Box 271, Folder 543)
      - Requests for campaign material, 1969 (Box 271, Folder 544)
      - Shrum, Bob, 1971 (Box 271, Folder 545)
      - Staten Island primary, 1969 (Box 271, Folder 546)
      - Steinberg, Mark, 1970-1971 (Box 271, Folder 547)
      - Summons abatement, 1966 (Box 271, Folder 548)
      - Support letters, JVL, 1968 (Box 271, Folder 549)
      - Support letters, JVL, 1969 (Box 271, Folder 550)
      - Task Force demolition, 1970 (Box 271, Folder 551)
      - Telegrams, 1970 (Box 271, Folder 552)
      - Thank-you letters for congratulations, 1966 (Box 271, Folder 553)
      - Thank-you letters for help, 1970 (Box 271, Folder 554)
      - Thank-you lists for thank-you letters, 1969 (Box 271, Folder 555)
      - Troy, Matther J., Jr., correspondence, memoranda, 1971 (Box 271, Folder 556)
    - Personal File, 1963-1969
      - Résumés and Job Applicants (Box 272, Folder 557-558)
    - Special Requests, 1967-1972
      - Brandi, James E., Jr., 1969-1971 (Box 273, Folder 559)
      - Job requests, Queens, 1972 (Box 273, Folder 560)
      - Liberal party of New York State (Ben Davidson, executive director), 1967-1969 (Box 273, Folder 561)
      - New York City Housing Authority
        - Bronx, 1967-1972 (Box 273, Folder 562-563)
        - Brooklyn, 1967-1972 (Box 273, Folder 564-566)
        - General (Box 274, Folder 567)
        - Manhattan, 1967-1971 (Box 274, Folder 568-569)
        - Queens, 1968-1973 (Box 274, Folder 570-571)
        - Staten Island, 1967-1972 (Box 274, Folder 572)
      - New York housing requests, 1964-1967 (Box 274, Folder 573)
      - New York Republican county committee (Mrs. Gertie Hess Parker), 1969 (Box 274, Folder 574)
      - Pinball machines in New York City, 1970 (Box 274, Folder 575)
      - Police department, applications and requests, 1967-1969 (Box 274, Folder 576)
      - Recommendations for housing and schools, 1969 (Box 274, Folder 577)
      - Special requests, miscellaneous, 1967, 1969 (Box 274, Folder 578-579)
      - Special requests, miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box 275, Folder 580-586)
      - Special requests, miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box 276, Folder 587-590)
      - Taxi commission, 1971 (Box 276, Folder 591)
      - Tenants association, 1970 (Box 276, Folder 592)
    - Job Appointments, 1965-1968
      - Addiction services agency (Box 277, Folder 593)
      - Assessors, board of (Box 277, Folder 594)
      - Board of estimates (Box 277, Folder 595)
      - Board of standards, appeals (Box 277, Folder 596)
      - Borough president of Queens (Box 277, Folder 597)
      - Budget, bureau (Box 277, Folder 598)
      - Buildings, department of (Box 277, Folder 599)
      - City planning commission (Box 277, Folder 600)
      - City record (Box 277, Folder 601)
      - City register (Box 277, Folder 602)
      - Civil Defense, office of (Box 277, Folder 603)
      - Davidson, Ben (Box 277, Folder 604)
      - Department placements, liberal lists (Box 277, Folder 605)
      - District attorney's office, Bronx (Box 277, Folder 606)
      - Finance, department of (Box 277, Folder 607)
      - Foss, Bill, letters for judicial appointments (Box 277, Folder 608)
      - Franchise (Box 277, Folder 609)
      - Housing authority (Box 277, Folder 610)
      - Job appointments (Box 277, Folder 611)
      - Landmarks (Box 277, Folder 612)
      - Marshals (Box 277, Folder 613)
      - Mayor's committee on the judiciary (Box 277, Folder 614)
      - Mayor's office (Box 277, Folder 615)
      - Medical examiner (Box 277, Folder 616)
      - Municipal broadcasting WNYC (Box 277, Folder 617)
      - Personnel (Box 277, Folder 618)
      - Police (Box 277, Folder 619)
      - Public officials, city government (Box 277, Folder 620-621)
      - Queens borough public library, honorary (Box 277, Folder 622)
      - Recommendations, Albano (Box 278, Folder 623-624)
      - Recommendations for job appointments (Box 278, Folder 625-630)
      - Transportation (Box 278, Folder 631)
    - Liberals, résumés and correspondence, 1966-1971
      - Brooklyn, pending referrals, 1966-1967 (Box 279, Folder 632)
      - Brooklyn, placed, 1965-1966 (Box 279, Folder 633)
      - Interviewed but not qualified, 1966 (Box 279, Folder 634)
      - Job applicants, 1966-1968 (Box 279, Folder 635-640)
      - Job applicants, 1966-1968 (Box 280, Folder 641-645)
      - Job applicants, 1965-1967 (Box 281, Folder 646-649)
      - Job applicants, 1966-1967 (Box 282, Folder 650)
      - Parks department, pending referral, 1966 (Box 282, Folder 651)
      - Personnel department, requests for letters of reply, 1966 (Box 282, Folder 652)
      - Queens, 1966 (Box 282, Folder 653)
      - Queens, pending, 1966 (Box 282, Folder 654)
      - Reinlieb, Julius, 1966 (Box 282, Folder 655)
      - Resumes, 1967-1971 (Box 282, Folder 656-657)
      - Seergy, Edmund G., 1966 (Box 282, Folder 658)
      - Volunteers, 1966 (Box 282, Folder 659)
      - Williams, Lloyd A., 1966 (Box 282, Folder 660)
      - Youth center, 1967 (Box 282, Folder 661)
    - Employees in Mayor's Office and Departments, 1970-1973
      - Appointed employees (Box 283, Folder 662)
      - Aurelio, weekly site selection status report and memoranda (Box 283, Folder 663)
      - Bramwell, Arthur, district leader (Box 283, Folder 664)
      - Caraballo, Dontzin, Leventhal, Davis (Box 283, Folder 665)
      - Council letters (Box 283, Folder 666)
      - Criminal justice coordinating council (Box 283, Folder 667)
      - Employees, mayor's office (Box 283, Folder 668)
      - Enviromental protection administration (Box 283, Folder 669)
      - Examination schedules (Box 283, Folder 670)
      - Feldstein, Lew, office (Box 283, Folder 671)
      - Feldstein, Lew, office (Box 284, Folder 672)
      - Fire (Box 284, Folder 673)
      - Health (Box 284, Folder 674)
      - Housing development administration (Box 284, Folder 675-676)
      - Human resources administration (Box 284, Folder 677)
      - Human Rights (Box 284, Folder 678)
      - Invitations accepted and regretted (Box 284, Folder 679)
      - Italians (Box 284, Folder 680)
      - Job descriptions (Box 285, Folder 681)
      - Jobs pending and placed (Box 285, Folder 682)
      - Kriegel, Eldridge (Box 285, Folder 683)
      - Liberals, placed or promoted (Box 285, Folder 684)
      - Liberals, resumes, lists, memoranda (Box 285, Folder 685)
      - Managerial pay plan (Box 285, Folder 686)
      - Mayor's office, general (Box 285, Folder 687)
      - Mayor's office, general (Box 286, Folder 688)
      - Mayor's office, Gottehrer (Box 286, Folder 689)
      - Mayor's office, Isenberg, Steve (Box 286, Folder 690)
      - Mayor's office, Morgan, Tom; Seifer, Nancy; Ortner, Charles (Box 286, Folder 691)
      - Model cities (Box 286, Folder 692)
      - Morrison, Carl (Box 286, Folder 693)
      - Off-track betting, applications submitted (Box 286, Folder 694-695)
      - Off-track betting, applications submitted (Box 287, Folder 696)
      - Off-track betting, hired from Auletta, Ken (Box 287, Folder 697)
      - Panetta, Leon (Box 287, Folder 698)
      - Parks (Box 287, Folder 699)
      - Party file (Box 287, Folder 700)
      - Personnel cuts (Box 287, Folder 701-702)
      - Queens, placed (Box 287, Folder 703)
      - Radley, Edie; St. John, Kathy (Box 287, Folder 704)
      - Resumes (Box 288, Folder 705)
      - Resumes, Democrats (Box 288, Folder 706)
      - Reviews (Box 288, Folder 707)
      - Root Tilden scholars (Box 288, Folder 708)
      - Talent search (Box 288, Folder 709)
      - Transportation (Box 288, Folder 710)
      - Tyler, Joel, interim source file (Box 288, Folder 711)
      - Ungar, Albert, correspondence and memoranda re: job requests (Box 288, Folder 712)
      - Water sheds (Box 288, Folder 713)
      - General Job Applications (Box 289, Folder 714-791)
      - General Job Applications (Box 290, Folder 792-883)
      - General Job Applications (Box 291, Folder 884-955)
      - General Job Applications (Box 292, Folder 956-1042)
      - General Job Applications (Box 293, Folder 1043-1130)
      - General Job Applications (Box 294, Folder 1131-1213)
      - General Job Applications (Box 295, Folder 1214-1299)
      - General Job Applications (Box 296, Folder 1300-1391)
      - General Job Applications (Box 297, Folder 1392-1434)
  - Nathan Leventhal (Assistant to the Mayor), 1970-1972; Series XV
    Series XV is sub-divided into four sections:
    Health Care
    Housing
    General Subject File
    - Health
      - Abortions and family planning (Box 298, Folder 1-2)
      - Abortion, newspaper articles, statistics (Box 298, Folder 3)
      - Alcoholism (Box 299, Folder 4-5)
      - Ambulatory care (Box 299, Folder 6)
      - Ambulance service survey (Box 300, Folder 7-9)
      - Board of Health (Box 301, Folder 10)
      - Capitol budget, health services (Box 301, Folder 11)
      - Child abuse (Box 301, Folder 12)
      - Cost control (Box 302, Folder 13)
      - Comprehensive health plan (Box 302, Folder 14-15)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force (Box 302, Folder 16-17)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, city wide consumer groups (Box 303, Folder 18)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, commerce and industry (Box 303, Folder 19)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, consumer payment organization (Box 303, Folder 20)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, council against poverty (Box 303, Folder 21)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, enviromental health (Box 303, Folder 22)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, labor (Box 303, Folder 23)
      - Comprehensive health plan, local consumer groups (Box 303, Folder 24)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, older New Yorkers (Box 303, Folder 25)
      - Comprehensive health plan, task force, regional planning organization (Box 303, Folder 26)
      - East Harlem environmental extension (Box 303, Folder 27)
      - Education (Box 303, Folder 28)
      - Financial health care (Box 303, Folder 29)
      - Ghetto medicine law (Box 303, Folder 30-31)
      - Governmental response, controls and ommissions (Box 303, Folder 32)
      - Group practice (Box 304, Folder 33)
      - Handicapped (Box 304, Folder 34-37)
      - Health care and public policy cases and materials, installments I-VI (Box 305, Folder 38-43)
      - Health education and welfare (Box 306, Folder 44)
      - Health and housing affairs (Box 306, Folder 45)
      - Health and hospitals (Box 306, Folder 46)
      - Health and hospital corporation (Box 306, Folder 47-48)
      - Health and hospital corporation (Box 307, Folder 49)
      - Health and hospital corporation cash flow (Box 307, Folder 50)
      - Health research council (Box 307, Folder 51-53)
      - Health services, information copies (Box 308, Folder 54)
      - Health Services Administration correspondence and memoranda (Box 308, Folder 55-61)
      - Health Services Administration correspondence and memoranda (Box 309, Folder 62-69)
      - Health Services Administration correspondence and memoranda (Box 310, Folder 70-74)
      - Health Services Administration weekly activity reports (Box 310, Folder 75)
      - Health Services Administration weekly activity reports (Box 311, Folder 76-78)
      - Hospital affiliation contracts (Box 311, Folder 79)
      - Hospital construction (Box 311, Folder 80)
      - Lead poisoning (Box 311, Folder 81)
      - Medical examiner (Box 311, Folder 82)
      - Medicaid, Medicare (Box 311, Folder 83)
      - Mental health (Box 312, Folder 84-88)
      - Mental health (Box 313, Folder 89)
      - Methadone treatment program (Box 313, Folder 90-93)
      - Nursing homes (Box 313, Folder 94)
      - Physician's assistance (Box 313, Folder 95)
      - Public hospital (Box 313, Folder 96)
    - Housing
      - Abandoned property (Box 314, Folder 97)
      - Administrative proceedures bill correspondence (Box 314, Folder 98)
      - Arlyn Gardens tenants (Box 314, Folder 99)
      - Board of standards and appeals (Box 314, Folder 100)
      - Capitol budget (Box 314, Folder 101)
      - Citizens' committee for children of New York (Box 314, Folder 102)
      - City council (Box 314, Folder 103-104)
      - City planning commission (Box 315, Folder 105)
      - Construction fact sheets (Box 315, Folder 106)
      - Emergency repair program (Box 315, Folder 107)
      - Federal code enforcement (Box 315, Folder 108)
      - Housing authority (Box 315, Folder 109)
      - Housing construction reports (Box 315, Folder 110)
      - Housing correspondence (Box 316, Folder 111)
      - Housing development administration (Box 316, Folder 112-114)
      - Housing form letters (Box 316, Folder 115)
      - Housing and health (Box 316, Folder 116)
      - Housing and health (Box 317, Folder 117)
      - Housing maintenance (Box 317, Folder 118)
      - Housing rent control (Box 317, Folder 119)
      - Housing urban development (Box 317, Folder 120-121)
      - Low cost housing (Box 317, Folder 122)
      - Mitchell-Lama Housing (Box 318, Folder 123)
      - Mobile homes (Box 318, Folder 124)
      - Model cities (Box 318, Folder 125-126)
      - New York City Housing Authority (Box 318, Folder 127)
      - Planning Commission correspondence (Box 319, Folder 128)
      - Policy planning council (Box 319, Folder 129)
      - Rent control letters (Box 319, Folder 130-131)
      - Rent increases, municipal loan program (Box 319, Folder 132)
      - Rent increases, exemptions, senior citizens (Box 319, Folder 133)
      - Rent and housing (Box 320, Folder 134)
      - South Richmond bill, Staten Island Marchi's development plan (Box 320, Folder 135)
      - Sub-contractors trade association (Box 320, Folder 136)
      - Urban housing discussion (Box 320, Folder 137)
      - Utilities, new buildings (Box 320, Folder 138)
      - Walsh, Al (Box 320, Folder 139)
    - General Subject Files
      - Agenda for cabinet meetings (Box 321, Folder 140)
      - Big six cities program (Box 321, Folder 141)
      - Board of estimate meetings (Box 321, Folder 142)
      - Board of standards and appeals (Box 321, Folder 143)
      - Cable TV, correspondence (Box 321, Folder 144)
      - Capitol budget, housing, health, education, police, parks, transportation (Box 321, Folder 145)
      - Congressman and senators, names, addresses, phone numbers (Box 321, Folder 146)
      - Consumer affairs (Box 321, Folder 147)
      - Drugs (Box 321, Folder 148)
      - East Harlem environmental extension service (Box 321, Folder 149)
      - Executive orders for city agency (Box 321, Folder 150)
      - Human resources administration (Box 321, Folder 151)
      - Jamaica, all American cities award (Box 322, Folder 152)
      - Legislation, state and federal (Box 322, Folder 153-156)
      - Mayor's projected schedule (Box 323, Folder 157)
      - Neighborhood government (Box 323, Folder 158)
      - Neighborhood redevelopment (Box 323, Folder 159)
      - Night Mayor's report (Box 323, Folder 160)
      - Old telephone lists (Box 323, Folder 161-162)
      - Old telephone messages (Box 324, Folder 163)
      - Opposition of issues, memoranda (Box 324, Folder 164)
      - Personnel (Box 324, Folder 165)
      - Police preventive control (Box 324, Folder 166)
      - Pollution (Box 324, Folder 167-169)
      - Press releases, memoranda, Washington news letter (Box 325, Folder 170-174)
      - Prison safety (Box 326, Folder 175)
      - Rat control, status reports, press releases, health, memoranda (Box 326, Folder 176)
      - Resumes, administrative (Box 326, Folder 177)
      - School bus safety (Box 326, Folder 178)
      - Staff meetings (Box 326, Folder 179)
      - Scheduling and date books (Box 326, Folder 179)
    - Correspondence and Memoranda
      - 1970 1970 (Box 327, Folder 180-185)
      - 1971 June-September 1971 June-September (Box 328, Folder 186-190)
      - 1971 October-November 1971 October-November (Box 329, Folder 191-194)
      - 1971 December-1972 February 1971 December-1972 February (Box 330, Folder 195-199)
      - 1972 March 1972 March (Box 331, Folder 200-201)
      - 1972 April 1972 April (Box 331, Folder 202-203)
      - 1972 May-June 1972 May-June (Box 332, Folder 204-207)
  - Jay Kriegel (Assistant to the Mayor), 1966-1973; Series XVI
    Series XVI is sub-divided into seven sections:
    Correspondence, 1966-1967
    Correspondence, 1967-1969
    Correspondence, 1969-1972
    General Subject File, 1966-1973
    Economic Development
    Narcotics
    Police Issues
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967
      - A (Box 333, Folder 1)
      - B (Box 333, Folder 2)
      - Ba (Box 333, Folder 3)
      - Be (Box 333, Folder 4)
      - Bl (Box 333, Folder 5)
      - Blackwell, Arthur (Box 333, Folder 6)
      - Br (Box 333, Folder 7)
      - Bu (Box 333, Folder 8)
      - C (Box 333, Folder 9)
      - Ca (Box 333, Folder 10)
      - Ce-Cl (Box 333, Folder 11)
      - Co-Cz (Box 333, Folder 12)
      - D (Box 333, Folder 13)
      - Da-Di (Box 333, Folder 14)
      - Do (Box 334, Folder 15)
      - Dr-Dz (Box 334, Folder 16)
      - E (Box 334, Folder 17)
      - F (Box 334, Folder 18)
      - Fa-Fe (Box 334, Folder 19)
      - Fi-Fz (Box 334, Folder 20)
      - Ga (Box 334, Folder 21)
      - Gar-Go (Box 334, Folder 22)
      - Gardner, Sid (Box 334, Folder 23)
      - Ginsbury, David (Box 334, Folder 24)
      - Goldmark, Peter (Box 334, Folder 25-27)
      - Gr-Gz (Box 334, Folder 28)
      - Greenfield, Jeff (Box 334, Folder 29)
      - Ha (Box 335, Folder 30)
      - Haacke, Harry (Box 335, Folder 31)
      - He-Hi (Box 335, Folder 32)
      - Ho-Hz (Box 335, Folder 33)
      - Hoberman, Solomon (Box 335, Folder 34)
      - Holtzman, Liz (Box 335, Folder 35)
      - I (Box 335, Folder 36)
      - J (Box 335, Folder 37)
      - Ka-Ki (Box 335, Folder 38)
      - Kl (Box 335, Folder 39)
      - La-Le (Box 335, Folder 40)
      - Li (Box 336, Folder 41)
      - Ma (Box 336, Folder 42)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 336, Folder 43)
      - McGarrahan, John (Box 336, Folder 44)
      - Me (Box 336, Folder 45)
      - N (Box 336, Folder 46)
      - O (Box 336, Folder 47)
      - Pa-Pe (Box 336, Folder 48)
      - Pi (Box 336, Folder 49)
      - Q (Box 336, Folder 50)
      - Ra-Re (Box 337, Folder 51)
      - Ros (Box 337, Folder 52)
      - Sa-Sc (Box 337, Folder 53)
      - Sc-Sm (Box 337, Folder 54)
      - Sn-St (Box 337, Folder 55)
      - Sturz, Herb (Box 337, Folder 56)
      - Su (Box 337, Folder 57)
      - T (Box 337, Folder 58)
      - U (Box 337, Folder 59)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969
      - A-B (Box 338, Folder 60-62)
      - C (Box 338, Folder 63-64)
      - G (Box 339, Folder 65-66)
      - H (Box 339, Folder 67-68)
      - I-J (Box 339, Folder 69)
      - M (Box 340, Folder 70-71)
      - N-Q (Box 340, Folder 72)
      - W (Box 340, Folder 73)
      - W-Z (Box 340, Folder 74-75)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972
      - A-Al (Box 341, Folder 76)
      - Am-Ar (Box 341, Folder 77)
      - As-Az (Box 341, Folder 78)
      - Aurelio, Richard (Box 341, Folder 79)
      - Bam-Baz (Box 341, Folder 80)
      - Bea-Bel (Box 341, Folder 81)
      - Ben-Ber (Box 341, Folder 82)
      - Berm-Bi (Box 341, Folder 83)
      - Bl-Blo (Box 341, Folder 84)
      - Blu-Boz (Box 341, Folder 85)
      - Botein, Bernard (Box 341, Folder 86)
      - Bra-Bro (Box 341, Folder 87)
      - Bru-Bz (Box 341, Folder 88)
      - Ca (Box 341, Folder 89)
      - Callendu, Eugene (Box 341, Folder 90)
      - Carballo, Manny (Box 341, Folder 91)
      - Ce-Cg (Box 341, Folder 92)
      - Ch-Cl (Box 341, Folder 93)
      - Co-Col (Box 341, Folder 94)
      - Com-Coz (Box 341, Folder 95)
      - Cr-Cz (Box 341, Folder 96)
      - Craco, Louis (Box 341, Folder 97)
      - Da (Box 341, Folder 98)
      - Davis, Gordon (Box 341, Folder 99)
      - De-Di (Box 341, Folder 100)
      - Do-Dr (Box 342, Folder 101)
      - Dodds, R. Harcourt (Box 342, Folder 102)
      - Dontzin, Michael J. (Box 342, Folder 103)
      - Ds-Dz (Box 342, Folder 104)
      - Ea-El (Box 342, Folder 105)
      - Em-Ez (Box 342, Folder 106)